Contact

djchadwick@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ danieljchadwick (LinkedIn) danielchadwick.co.uk (Blog)

Top Skills

PHP

C#

SQL

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

98-367: MTA: Security

Fundamentals

98-368: MTA: Mobility and Device

Fundamentals

98-375: MTA: HTML5 Application Development Fundamentals

98-349: MTA: Windows® Operating

System Fundamentals

98-365: MTA: Windows® Server Administration Fundamentals

Daniel Chadwick

Junior PHP Developer at Wren Kitchens

Hull, United Kingdom

Summary

Graduate Computer Science Student at the University of Hull. Currently working at Wren Kitchens as a Junior PHP Developer. Prior to studying, I worked for 2 years at an online eCommerce Workwear Retailer as a Full Stack Apprentice working on PHP store management systems, scripts and data analysis. Whilst at University I studied mainly C# but have worked with Java, C++, C and JavaScript.

Experience

Wren Kitchens
Junior PHP Developer
June 2019 - Present

Barton-upon-Humber, North Lincolnshire, United Kingdom

Currently working with:

- Symfony 4
- Doctrine ORM (MySQL)
- JavaScript
- RabbitMQ (AMQP)
- PHP7
- Twig
- CSS (Less)
- Docker
- RESTful APIs
- Testing (PHPUnit/Behat)
- Elasticsearch

Workwear Outlet
Full Stack Apprentice
January 2015 - September 2016 (1 year 9 months)
Blackburn, United Kingdom

Education

The University of Hull
Bachelor's Degree (Hons), Computer Science · (2016 - 2019)

QA Apprenticeships

Apprenticeship training, Level 3 ICT Systems and Principles / ICT Professional Competence · (2015 - 2016)

Ribblesdale High School 9 GCSEs A* - B · (2009 - 2014)